LUCKY MAYALDHI

Frontend Engineer / Software Developer



work.mayaldhi@gmail.com



PROFILE

I am passionate about software and technology. I absolutely love writing codes and enjoys learning something new. I've been working as a Front end Developer for more than 1 year and I'm looking for an opportunity to improve my interpersonal skills.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Java
- Jquery
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- Next.js

EDUCATION

Diploma, Management Informatics

Gunadarma University

2015 - 2020

Multimedia

SMK Islam PB. Soedirman 1

2013 - 2015

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

id/x partners

2021 - 2022

- Optimizing the user experience
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Get feedback from, and build solutions for, users and customers

Frontend Developer

Kindly Creative Production

2020 - 2021

- Prioritizing user experience
- Production and maintenance of websites user interfaces
- Responsible for the translation of UI/UX design wireframes to actual code.